Today we are shooting a music video for a song we can't lose.
Yay!
I'm in the car now.
Hi! Hello.
Mr. Curry is here, too.
Let's see..,
We're all dressed in white today.
It's totally different,
Oh, here we are.
Oh, is it that big?
Wow! Wow! It's huge!
Anyway, I was told to move to the tent,
I'd like to see the shooting site,
I'm going!
Mr. Curry is running right now.
Amazing! Oh, Shinji-chan!
Shinji-chan, come running.
Where's home?
What is your home?
Where's your home?
Written by Yuna Hazuki.
Written by Mr. Hazuki.
Mr. Hadoki. That's great! Wait a minute.
This is amazing.
This one is beautiful, isn't it?
Yuna, it's beautiful, isn't it?
Yes! So..,
Here we are!
Hawaii!
Yes! That's right,
Today's destination,
Hawaii!
Look at the view!
Wow! It's so beautiful!
So, here we are,
From Hawaii
I'd like to give a quiz to everyone in the studio
I would like to give you a quiz!
Today we have
Miyu Fujitani, who is in the studio today,
Please answer the question!
Yes!
Speaking of Hawaii,
Loco moco,
What does "loco moco" mean?
What does moco mean?
Takeh!
Taken!
Bamboo?
Pppp!
The correct answer is,
Hawaiians are actually fond of something called Fluffy.
Because Hawaiian people actually like the material called "Fluffy",
Hey!
What is this?
Today,
The music video for the song "I Can't Open the Door
for the music video for the song "Open Door"!
Today, we are meeting at 7:00 in the morning.
schedule.
Yesterday
I had a lesson yesterday, too,
Live performance is happening.
Yay!
I can't open my eyes.
My ears are glued.
I'll do my best. From now on.
Gouge your ears.
Keep your sides tight,
If you don't keep your psoas muscles in front of your face
Or your fans will get angry.
Yes!
Today,
I'm shooting a music video for a song I'm not going to open.
It's a very nice
location.
For now,
Who is that?
Lung-chan is painting.
Oh! Here comes Suzi.
The second Cinderella!
She is a cheerful girl today.
I am,
I have a theme. This time
costume. I'm Old Idol,
I'm an old idol and a cheerful girl.
Lun-chan is an angel.
We all have something. Ask them.
Oh, here comes the gal.
All right!
What a great idea,
It's like a work of art.
It's one of a kind.
Emo!
I can only draw on this fan.
Emo emo emo.
Sun emo.
See, it's beautiful.
It's not dirty.
Don't make it dirty.
Do your best not to get it dirty.
Kiss.
I'm looking at you.
When the camera is pointed at me,
I don't know what to do.
For the sake of your idol.
Eating.
I'm going to eat it.
I didn't eat.
She said she was still hungry.
I ate.
It wasn't good.
It's supposed to be good.
She said she ate it in without any heart.
Lightly.
Light.
Parfik pie.
Palfik pie.
Hello.
Seino.
It's bovine time.
Usakoji channel.
Usakoji Channel.
Runchan is
Paint.
The finish is ready.
Finished.
What's the theme of your outfit today, Run-chan?
An angel.
Angel.
I'm a cheerful girl.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
See you later.
How did that happen?
He's tracing me.
Was the camera rolling?
He's grinning.You're grinning.
Why the hand?
You should dress up a little more.
You're wearing a tan.
I do it this way.
He's wearing it like this.
He's wearing a tan.
But it's still not here, is it?
There's a little more, isn't there?
This is paint that won't come off.
Is it? Is it?
Is that so?
I'm so surprised.
It's going to stay like this for the rest of my life.
When we were fist-fighting.
Quickly.
Oh, shit. There's a girl peeking.
There's a girl peeking.
I'm peeking from a dangerous place.
There's a kid peeking.
I'll get ready.
He's cute.
He's got a smile on his face.
Here she comes.
Cute.
It's a zombie movie.
Today we are shooting a zombie movie.
Today is a zombie movie.
It's prettier than paint.
Thank you.
It's nice.
If I say "these two", it's a zombie movie.
If I say these two are in a zombie movie, it's a zombie movie.
I'm going to imitate a tyrannosaurus.
I'll imitate Tyrannosaurus.
It's good.
Then we'll go home.
That's the style I'm going home from there.
I'm gone.
Look at this.
What is it?
The door is about to open.
I almost opened the door.
This is going to be a hobby of mine.
I'm going to make a hobby of you.
I thought of myself as weak and unreliable.
I thought I was weak and unreliable.
I have such dependable allies.
I cry every time I sing.
It's really as it is.
It really is just as it is.
Great lyrics.
It's exactly as it is.
Yes, it is.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
That was good.
That's good.
It's OK.
That sucks.
Other.
Another.
I'm going to write this for all three of us at the same time.
I'm going to write this with all three of you at the same time.
OK.
Good, good, good.
The night sky is amazing.
It's cold.
It looks like a man, doesn't it?
It looks like a man.
It's a boy.
It won't shift, will it?
Everybody stand up.
Sei-no.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Yes, OK.
Yes, cut.
Yes, it's okay to shoot.
Yes, thank you.
Let's break it up a little bit.
Yes, OK.
You don't have to splash around in there.
I'll try a little more toward the Kamitegawa River.
Yes, OK.
OK.
M, O, N, BON!
I, Yoshin Tachibana, will now write the title of the song you can't lose.
I will do my best.
Don't get mad at me.
Thank you.
I'm nervous.
The kanji is right, right?
It's going to be the title, so I'm serious.
Should I write it bigger?
I'm so nervous.
Here it is.
It's right, isn't it?
Write it like this.
Write it big.
Do you want it a little thicker? Is that okay?
It's fine. It's fine.
I wrote it.
You wrote it.
It's big.
It's the last spurt.
Thank you.
The end.
Ready.
I won't lose.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Cuts.
Thank you, Mr. Nagashima.
Thank you very much.
Amazing.
Thank you so much.
We are really looking forward to the reflection and us too.
Thank you for just being really cold.
Thank you very much.
That's all!
UCHIRA! The sound of Nishibata!
Iginari! I had a great time!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.